<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Khaled Abou Alfa</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/kaa&quot;&gt;@kaa on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://www.kaa.bz/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 06:35:59 +0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 06:35:59 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Missing from Micro.blog</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I don’t like to write about &lt;em&gt;the system&lt;/em&gt; I’m using but I thought it would be good to check in a couple of times a year and see the lay of the land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Micro.blog is a personal online publishing platform with a social layer built in. It differs from other publishing platforms in a few key ways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It actively encourages you to use your own domain name.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It’s simple to publish.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For some it is a paid service.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It provides you with &lt;strong&gt;some&lt;/strong&gt; stats.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It provides you with &lt;strong&gt;some&lt;/strong&gt; control of what your site looks like.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The social element is managed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that Micro.blog handles many issues in a wonderfully elegant fashion. However there is plenty of room for improvement. While I’m aware that &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/manton&quot;&gt;@manton&lt;/a&gt; is but one person who is already doing a lot, it’s important to recognise that the sustainable thing is to have more than one person involved in the ongoing development of the platform, dare I say &lt;em&gt;multiple&lt;/em&gt; people. To help him get to that ideal, the hosted option &lt;strong&gt;needs&lt;/strong&gt; to become more appealing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-canonical-app&quot;&gt;The Canonical App&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m not going to focus on any of the apps that have been made for Micro.blog (official or third party), as I see these as nice to haves. For me the canonical view is the one presented at the website. This is the view that &lt;em&gt;everyone&lt;/em&gt; on the platform shares (regardless of operating system). I think overall the simplicity of this interface is what makes things work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Items that I would like to see included at some point:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Let me filter the type of posts from people I follow. So if I want to see everyone’s photos then let me do that. Let me see everyone’s podcasts. Sure you can do something similar from the discover section, but that’s everyone (?) on the platform.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It would be nice to see how many responses have been made on any individual post. Could be a small little number next to the ‘conversation’ link.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Allow more than one photo to be uploaded at a time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Highlight the emojis that are supported on the platform directly underneath and allow you to insert them from there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;photos&quot;&gt;Photos&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photos should be showcased on a grid of three squares across. Ideally this should be another standard page found at &lt;em&gt;mydomain/photos&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Micro.blog already is able to distinguish photos pretty well. Let me see my photos in a gallery. It’s one of the feature that made me stick with Instagram for as long as I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;stats&quot;&gt;Stats&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Micro.blog does not, by design, show the number of users that follow you. My view on stats is that as this site is focused on my words and pictures, then my stats should also focus on this output.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would love to see a yearly view of the number of posts I’ve made on a month by month basis. Each month could have two bars showing how much stuff gets posted to my site and how much stuff is interaction with others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additional stats could highlight the total number of photos, posts and interactions. What is the number of people I am following (I can see this in the iOS app but not on the web).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason for this is simple. It’s gamifying the experience. Except I’m now in competition with my previous self.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;subscription&quot;&gt;Subscription&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/manton/1057209&quot;&gt;finally being offered&lt;/a&gt;, but not &lt;em&gt;officially&lt;/em&gt; (blink that reply and it’s gone)? I’d like to see a yearly subscription to the service become official.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;two-streams&quot;&gt;Two Streams&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Micro.blog by it’s nature has two streams. The first is your website stream, and only includes your posts, while the second stream is the social one that includes everyone you follow and your posts starting with an @ symbol. As a user both are important, yet they are given wildly different treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your contributions to the conversation are still your words. These are currently only found in &lt;em&gt;micro.blog/yourusername.&lt;/em&gt; I would say that these should either be allowed to be ‘published’ to your blog as part of your stream or captured in a separate page with a link back to the original conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;design&quot;&gt;Design&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I initially used to love the fact that I was limited in what I could do which was to play around with the CSS and that was it. Since then the addition of updating the footer has been added. A great additions for sure, but I want full control of my site. I’m paying for hosting, eventually I’d like to be allowed to control the whole look of my site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recognise that this is likely a much more involved design change, but it’s one that I think is important to provide as an option, so that there isn’t a pretty fundamental reason to go self host and attach an RSS feed in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;categories&quot;&gt;Categories&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are currently 9 categories that you can contribute towards. It’s a good start, but hardly what I’d call comprehensive. I’d like to see a great deal more categories. Architecture, Engineering, Comics, Stationary, Country-specific-categories, and the list goes on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clearly part of a much larger project, which may require the recruitment of moderators in this space, but again it needs to expand to allow people to huddle around the digital campfire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;expectations&quot;&gt;Expectations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I absolutely understand how things have improved over the last 10 months since using the service and that I’m effectively providing some ideas/thoughts about how the service would become even more enjoyable for me.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 06:35:22 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/19/missing-from-microblog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/19/missing-from-microblog.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The new Smashing Pumpkins album is such a treat for us fans. &lt;em&gt;Solara&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Alienation&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Marchin’ On&lt;/em&gt; being the stand out songs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 17:48:52 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/18/the-new-smashing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/18/the-new-smashing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Years ago, while in London, I would often turn to the movie &lt;em&gt;Amelie&lt;/em&gt; in an attempt to help me relax, try be more positive about the world and life in general. All these years later it still does the trick.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 22:29:23 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/17/years-ago-while.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/17/years-ago-while.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m &lt;em&gt;kinda&lt;/em&gt; over stationary. Once you’ve tried a bunch of things and realised that you have what suits your needs (and more), the continued hunt becomes hoarding. I have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.penchalet.com/reviews/sailor_1911_black_luster_fountain_pen_review.html&quot;&gt;one big purchase&lt;/a&gt; left before I close the book on this hobby for a while.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 21:10:04 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/17/im-kinda-over.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/17/im-kinda-over.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I always end up surfing the web looking at a bunch of awesome t-shirts. Then I realise that they’re all super expensive (once you add shipping) and just close the tab depressed.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 07:14:35 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/16/i-always-end.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/16/i-always-end.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The John Lewis Christmas adverts are an institution. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mNbSgMEZ_Tw&quot;&gt;latest one&lt;/a&gt; is by far one of my absolute favourites.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 19:43:34 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/15/the-john-lewis.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/15/the-john-lewis.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Totally underwhelmed by the new Field Notes Winter release, &lt;a href=&quot;https://fieldnotesbrand.com/products/clandestine&quot;&gt;Clandestine&lt;/a&gt;. The video though has got the best production values I’ve seen from them. Not for me though, as I’ve got enough FNs to last me 3-4 years at least.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 22:17:03 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/13/totally-underwhelmed-by.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/13/totally-underwhelmed-by.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?time_continue=95&amp;amp;v=nQk7DWW4mz8&quot;&gt;Great trailer&lt;/a&gt; for Toy Story 4. I only found out that this was happening earlier this morning. Had the same feeling as Duckie there, alas they’ve won me over.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 22:09:06 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/13/great-trailer-for.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/13/great-trailer-for.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;He had a &lt;strong&gt;great&lt;/strong&gt; run, but alas  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.comicsbeat.com/stan-lee-has-died/&quot;&gt;Stan Lee has died&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 23:33:57 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/12/he-has-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/12/he-has-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;First rain have come with thunder and lightning. It’s been such a long time since we’ve had any rainfall in the Gulf.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 20:51:02 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/11/first-rain-have.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/11/first-rain-have.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Crescent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/5a54739555.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 18:04:59 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/10/the-creacent.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/10/the-creacent.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Awesome analysis of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.arun.is/blog/custom-typefaces/&quot;&gt;why tech companies are making custom typefaces.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 17:48:19 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/10/awesome-analysis-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/10/awesome-analysis-of.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Podcasts for November</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎙️ Seeing as I’m in the car for many hours of the day (travelling up and down to Abu Dhabi), I’ve been listening to a ton of podcasts recently….a metric ton in fact. Here are some of the highlight episodes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://podtail.com/podcast/unfiltered-with-james-o-brien-joe/sir-nick-clegg-live-by-the-sword-die-by-the-sword/&quot;&gt;Unfiltered interview with Sir Nick Clegg&lt;/a&gt; - essential listening if you’re looking to understand Brexit more.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://serialpodcast.org/season-three/about&quot;&gt;Serial Season Three&lt;/a&gt; - I missed season 2, but this season has been very good.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://songexploder.net/halloween&quot;&gt;Song Exploder - John Carpenter Halloween Theme&lt;/a&gt; - Was made even better as we drove in pitch darkness on a moonless night.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cms.megaphone.fm/channel/broken-record&quot;&gt;Broken Record&lt;/a&gt; - Hey, it’s Malcolm Gladwell.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 23:13:54 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/09/podcasts-for-november.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/09/podcasts-for-november.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Park season is upon us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/27d0648f37.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:47:27 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/09/park-season-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/09/park-season-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The weekend is finally upon us and as always I’m hopeful of filling it with good activities for both myself and the rest of the family. It’s not so much living for the weekend as it making the most of the weekends which offer more time than the week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 19:19:23 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/08/the-weekend-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/08/the-weekend-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been an exceptionally tough week, which is to be expected as everyone is working on overdrive towards the imminent opening for Qasr Al Hosn in Abu Dhabi. &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/QasrAlHosn/status/1059785724113883137&quot;&gt;Great video&lt;/a&gt; on the Twitter feed.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 16:18:29 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/08/121829.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/08/121829.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Finding your niche can feel like a life long struggle. Some discover it early on and continue to build on that discovery. Others meander through life until they settle. While other due to circumstance or ability never reach that discovery. You have one life. Go. Discover.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 06:05:16 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/05/finding-your-niche.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/05/finding-your-niche.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This weekend’s mini project was making an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lomography.com/magazine/336973-lomography-tutorials-adjustable-snake-knot-camera-strap&quot;&gt;adjustable snake knot camera strap&lt;/a&gt;. Went for some funky colours as the paracord on offer had limited colours available. If you have to go bold, go all the way.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 16:24:26 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/03/this-weekends-mini.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/03/this-weekends-mini.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/60d6ab54fd.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;398&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 22:57:38 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/02/185738.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/02/185738.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/679df47b1b.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;398&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 11:15:53 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/02/071553.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/02/071553.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;All of my &lt;em&gt;writing&lt;/em&gt; happens in &lt;a href=&quot;http://ia.net&quot;&gt;iAWriter&lt;/a&gt;. All of my &lt;em&gt;editing&lt;/em&gt; is happening in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hemingwayapp.com&quot;&gt;Hemingway app&lt;/a&gt;. If you’ve not used this app, go read the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hemingwayapp.com/help.html&quot;&gt;help&lt;/a&gt; section first then give it a try on something you’ve written. It’s eye-opening.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 22:35:13 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/01/183513.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/01/183513.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As much as I love October, really glad it’s finally over and can look forward to what November has to bring. Winter is finally upon us and I’m looking forward to enjoying the outdoors a little bit more. With both boys in tow I’m hoping for a bunch of fun over the next 6 months.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 20:24:33 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/11/01/as-much-as.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/11/01/as-much-as.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;First proper halloween experience for Zane, which he absolutely loved. Got dressed as a pterodactyl, hunted for houses with their lights on and then stuffing his bucket with goodies. I’ve never been into Halloween, but starting to enjoy it through my kid’s eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 20:36:14 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/31/first-proper-halloween.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/31/first-proper-halloween.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This new iPad Pro is a great way to finally get into the iPad lifestyle. Glad I waited out for this version (rather than getting one last year). Hopefully it’ll be my upgraded computing device for the next five years.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 21:21:11 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/30/this-new-ipad.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/30/this-new-ipad.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for a great alternative to the standard Apple case for your iPhone 6, 6s, 7 and 8, look no further than the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.puro.it/en/cover-icon-iphone8-eng.html&quot;&gt;Puro Icon&lt;/a&gt; case. Got mine in an amazing aquamarine colour.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 11:58:05 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/26/075805.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/26/075805.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re struggling to write on your site, then consider a trick I’ve been using this year. I write for myself and  1 other person that doesn’t exist, except in my mind. He likes similar things as me, and my site is how I share small messages with him.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 05:24:30 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/24/if-youre-struggling.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/24/if-youre-struggling.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Inktober #005 continues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/956d937b9a.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 16:33:37 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/23/inktober-continues.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/23/inktober-continues.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Inktober is nearly over. This one was done while I was on the phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/8f40d272ed.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 07:45:01 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/23/inktober-is-nearly.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/23/inktober-is-nearly.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Went to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bigbadwolfbooks.com&quot;&gt;Big Bad Wold book&lt;/a&gt; fair (the biggest of it’s kind in the world). It’s so massive that people wander around with supermarket shopping carts filled will books. For my first trip I picked up:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Graphic Ink by Frank Quietley&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Wake by Scott Snyder and Sean Murphy&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Comics A Global History by Dan Mazur and Alexander Danner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 06:00:06 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/21/went-to-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/21/went-to-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;📚 Autumn reading. Second Ryan Holiday book this year. I still need to write the notes from my previous two books. Maybe this week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/bf461b09f8.jpg&quot; width=&quot;599&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 09:46:51 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/20/autumn-reading-second.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/20/autumn-reading-second.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apple.com/apple-events/&quot;&gt;You’re testing me Apple&lt;/a&gt;. I’ve abstained from your iPhone ploy this year (even though I’m sporting an iPhone 6S), but I’ve never owned an iPad and I’m running a 5 year old Macbook Pro, which is closing in on upgrade territory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/e7b1f1195f.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;389&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 23:02:46 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/18/190246.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/18/190246.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to create something, anything really, then I seriously encourage you to listen to Seth Godin’s podcast &lt;em&gt;Akimbo&lt;/em&gt;. The previous episode, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.akimbo.me/blog/s-3-e-2-you-re-it&quot;&gt;You’re it&lt;/a&gt; seriously captures the reason that you should start NOW with that endeavour. Don’t wait. You’re wasting time. As am I.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 22:47:40 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/18/if-youre-looking.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/18/if-youre-looking.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Operation &lt;em&gt;start using your iPhone less and take your Sony mirrorless camera everywhere&lt;/em&gt; is beginning to pay some dividends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/e7b1b97fd9.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;399&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 22:05:20 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/16/operation-start-using.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/16/operation-start-using.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Discovered &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thenational.ae/lifestyle/food/burro-blanco-the-tiny-hole-in-the-wall-bringing-mexican-street-food-to-abu-dhabi-1.751906#10&quot;&gt;Burro Blanco&lt;/a&gt; in Abu Dhabi a couple of weeks ago. By far my favourite Mexican restaurant in the UAE.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 22:12:30 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/15/discovered-burro-blanco.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/15/discovered-burro-blanco.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Definitely considering backing this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/twinzstudio/everyday-carry-aerospace-grade-titanium-chopsticks&quot;&gt;chopstick set&lt;/a&gt;. The straw might now be as useful for me, but I really like the chopsticks rest and pouch. Super neat solution.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 05:48:57 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/15/definitely-considering-backing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/15/definitely-considering-backing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/867313368/dutch-type-the-book-available-again&quot;&gt;Jan Middendorp’s &lt;em&gt;Dutch Type&lt;/em&gt; is truly a magnificent book&lt;/a&gt;. I would go so far as to call it the best looking book on typography that I own. If you can get a copy, don’t hesitate. Gorgeous.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 22:27:16 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/14/jan-middendorps-dutch.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/14/jan-middendorps-dutch.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Final Inktober image for today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/0329a5efbd.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 18:11:35 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/13/final-inktober-image.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/13/final-inktober-image.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The constraint for Inktober this year is the number of pens I’m using and the size of paper, which are these super cheap postcards from Muji (12 for less than a dollar).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/5b1996f15b.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 18:10:12 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/13/the-constraint-for.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/13/the-constraint-for.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I know I’m super late to Inktober this year, but better late than never.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/f69d8f0913.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 18:04:19 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/13/140419.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/13/140419.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I can finally declare Autumn/Winter has begun here in Dubai. It’s been a really long summer so hoping to make full advantage of the good weather this year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 15:24:58 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/13/i-can-finally.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/13/i-can-finally.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My wife is forever loosing her iPhone. &lt;strong&gt;Top tip&lt;/strong&gt;. If you login from another device on iCloud (and assuming the phone is still got power and connected to the internet) you can cause it to ring, even if it’s put on mute. So awesome.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 19:37:45 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/12/my-wife-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/12/my-wife-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Phones and Cameras</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After listen to &lt;em&gt;The Minimalists&lt;/em&gt; on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kevinrose.com&quot;&gt;Kevin Rose&lt;/a&gt; show, I came to a realisation. In my persuit to determine which iPhone I should be buying this year, it turns out I really don’t need to get one after all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason for upgrading isn’t because the phone is slow, lacks some essential feature or that certain apps don’t run on it. Rather the &lt;strong&gt;only&lt;/strong&gt; reason to upgrade is for the camera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Except I already own a pretty decent camera, the NEX-F3. I bought it just before Zane was born (so a little over 4 years ago now) and seem to have stopped using it 2 years ago. Why? I’m not sure. Maybe I bought into the whole ‘the best camera is the one on you’ ideaology?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A quick read of a Wirecutter &lt;a href=&quot;https://thewirecutter.com/reviews/first-sony-e-mount-lenses-to-buy/&quot;&gt;article I bookmarked in 2013&lt;/a&gt;, led me to circling onto several Sigma lens that will help me get better photos. The bonus to all this is that they’re at a pretty reduced price point at the moment. And while we’re here, we might as well talk about one of &lt;a href=&quot;https://prolost.com/blog/2013/12/11/how-to-take-good-photos-for-under-1000.html&quot;&gt;my favourite article&lt;/a&gt; about photography to brush up on some things.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 21:55:55 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/10/phones-and-cameras.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/10/phones-and-cameras.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Netflix has seriously changed how I consume some of my entertainment. Thankfully &lt;em&gt;Better Call Saul&lt;/em&gt; isn’t on that network which means I have to wait for a new episode every week. Somehow gives my week a little bit of relief as it’s the only show I’m watching these days.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 20:34:46 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/08/netflix-has-seriously.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/08/netflix-has-seriously.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I stumbled upon a truly incredible graph today that showed all the various types of Photovoltaic panel technology and their efficiency progress mapped across the years. What’s astounding is the innovation that is happening in this space, showing where the future will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/35f115b2b3.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;333&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 21:09:51 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/04/i-stumbled-upon.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/04/i-stumbled-upon.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://inktober.com&quot;&gt;Happy Inktober everyone&lt;/a&gt;. I’m hoping to dip my toe this year and have an idea of what to do, hopefully ready with a few things to share.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 19:41:26 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/03/happy-inktober-everyone.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/03/happy-inktober-everyone.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Everything old is new again. New faces in the office as our team slowly continues it’s transformation. I’m obviously aware (sometimes painfully) that nothing in life stays the same. When life kicks your ass, first tidy everything up and then assess and review.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 19:30:12 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/10/02/everything-old-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/10/02/everything-old-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Finally got the bluetooth in my car sorted out. It’s only taken a couple of years and $100 to get it sorted. I’ll never understand why Audi don’t enable this simple feature to begin with but there you have it. Now I can listen to my tunes through proper speakers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 20:48:35 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/09/30/finally-got-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/09/30/finally-got-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s getting easier to draw these scenes. The funny thing being that once I gave up on drawing comics I’ve allowed myself to draw these types of things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/da6232bd17.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 19:47:16 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/09/27/its-getting-easier.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/09/27/its-getting-easier.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Ok I’ve not bought any new Field Notes in a year. I still have a healthy stash and could easily remain stocked up for several years to come….&lt;em&gt;however&lt;/em&gt; these &lt;a href=&quot;https://fieldnotesbrand.com/products/rams&quot;&gt;Ram edition&lt;/a&gt; are really testing my Field Notes abstinence.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 22:46:02 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/09/24/ok-ive-not.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/09/24/ok-ive-not.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;These three &lt;a href=&quot;http://f1.com/2021&quot;&gt;F1 2021&lt;/a&gt; concepts as revealed on the F1 website show a future of motosport that &lt;em&gt;looks&lt;/em&gt; exciting. They’re also meant delivers to deliver closer driving and wheel to wheel action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.kaa.bz/uploads/2018/3333774548.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;337&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 17:44:24 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.kaa.bz/2018/09/23/these-f-concepts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kaa.micro.blog/2018/09/23/these-f-concepts.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
